A.D.
M.
Due to its declining birthrate of the human popula- tion,
Akibat dari turunnya tingkat kelahiran populasi manusia,
this country has turned into a nation of cats.
negara ini menjadi negeri para kucing.
Cat Country Japan.
Negara Kucing Jepang
Mugishima,
Mugishima,
I heard our school allows part-time jobs.
Dengar-dengar, sekolah kita mengizinkan kerja paruh waktu, loh.
Sora and Part-Time Job
Sora dan Kerja Paruh Waktu
Oh, is that so?
Oh, iya kah?
"Experience is what enriches life,"
"Pengalaman itu memperkaya hidup,"
I suppose that's the idea behind it.
mungkin seperti itu maksudnya.
Sora, do you want to get a part-time job?
Sora, kamu tertarik cari kerja paruh waktu?
Mitten Fair
Mitten Fair
It's so warm!
Hangat sekali!
A part-time job, huh?
Kerja paruh waktu, ya…
Should we get one together?
Bagaimana kalau kita kerja bareng?
Are you sure?
Beneran nih?
You two can start today, welcome.
Baik, kalian bisa mulai hari ini. Selamat bergabung.
It's great that we both got hired, isn't it?
Senang ya, kita berdua langsung diterima.
Mugishima, are you working the register?
Mugishima, bagianmu di kasir, ya?
That sounds interesting.
Kelihatannya asyik.
Well then, I'm heading over to my ticket station.
Kalau begitu, aku ke pos tiketku dulu, ya.
Okay, good luck.
Oke, semangat.
Huh? Why he's heading to ticket station?
Eh? Pos tiket?
I think that's all.
Ini saja pesanannya.
Please take the number 2 cat and have a seat while you wait.
Silakan ambil kucing nomor 2, lalu silakan tunggu di tempat duduk.
Order for number 2 cat.
Pesanan untuk kucing nomor 2.
Your order is ready.
Silahkan diambil.
I'm starting to get the hang of this whole 'ticket duty' thing.
Kurasa aku sudah mulai terbiasa dengan pekerjaan ini.
Have you gotten used to the work?
Kamu sudah terbiasa dengan pekerjaanmu?
A little.
Lumayan.
Mugishima, you're a real natural.
Mugishima, kamu cepat belajar, ya.
You're a fast learner,
Kamu juga cepat tanggap.
and as the manager, you can take my word for it.
dan sebagai manajer kamu, aku bisa jamin itu.
Well, I guess it's about time I showed Sora his duties as well.
Baiklah, sepertinya sudah waktunya aku ajari Sora tugasnya juga.
Oh, I've pretty much memorized the tickets already.
Oh, aku sudah hafal semua nomor tiketnya, kok.
Hmm? There's nothing to memorize about the tickets.
Lho? Memangnya ada yang perlu dihafal dari tiket?
Huh? There isn't?
Eh? Nggak ada, ya?
Heave… ho…
Satu… dua…
Thank you for waiting, here's your cheeseburger.
Permisi, ini pesanan cheeseburger-nya.
The rest of the drinks are heavy,
Minumannya lumayan berat,
so could you please go get them yourself?
jadi, bisa tolong diambil sendiri?
Thank you for your cooperation.
Mohon pengertiannya, ya.
What's even the point of that waiter?
Jadi guna pramusaji tadi apaan ya?
TL TM TS MX-QC AI Transcribe was utilized
TL TM TS MX-QC AI Transcribe diutilisasikan
: geckyzz
: geckyzz